<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Phoenix Real Estate Video Blog with Monique Walker</title>
    <description>Our mission at Monique Walker Team is to be your best resource for Phoenix real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Monique Walker Team, your professional Phoenix Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 13:11:24 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 13:11:24 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate 101: How Realtors Help You Sell Your Home</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/YHW8VONCTAs?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re young or old, real estate can be a tricky thing to wrap your head around. For many people who are new to the market, it’s often helpful to explain things in the simplest way possible. I like to educate buyers and sellers in a way that’s incredibly easy to grasp — in fact, it’s so straightforward that even kids can understand it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Although most of these steps can be a lot more in-depth, this is generally how we progress through the home selling process.%20http://localhost:4000/real-estate-101-how-realtors-help-you-sell-your-home.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Although most of these steps can be a lot more in-depth, this is generally how we progress through the home selling process.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With the help of my daughter, today I’ll be explaining the seven steps a Realtor takes when helping someone sell their home:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The seller calls the Realtor.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Realtor does a walk-through of the house. A walk-through means going through the home and checking out its features, upgrades, and condition.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Realtor determines the price. They usually do this by seeing what similar homes sold for recently.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Realtor lists the home on the multiple listing service (MLS). This online platform is where Realtors post a home so that other Realtors and homebuyers can see it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Realtor shows the property to people who want to buy the house.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Realtor negotiates with the buyer and their Realtor to find out what they’re willing to pay for the house.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The home is sold! However, it still takes about 30 days before the sale is completed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although most of these steps can be a lot more in-depth, this is generally how we progress through the home selling process. If you have any questions or would like more information about buying or selling a home, feel free to reach out to me. &lt;strong&gt;I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 11:10:47 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/real-estate-101-how-realtors-help-you-sell-your-home.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/real-estate-101-how-realtors-help-you-sell-your-home.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What’s on the Menu at the Fat Ox?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/HYha9Ny2uzs?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m visiting the Fat Ox restaurant in central Scottsdale to chat with head chef and owner Matt Carter. Located just a few minutes from Old Town Scottsdale and within walking distance of the new Ritz-Carlton being built, the Fat Ox is in one of the most amazing corners you can be in. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Matt is also the head chef at Zinc Bistro and The Mission. Even before he opened Zinc Bistro 20 years ago, Matt wanted to open an Italian restaurant and explore Italian cuisine and the similar products we have here in Arizona such as figs, olives, and citrus. Additionally, a lot of the wheat that’s grown in Italy is also grown in the Southwest. According to Matt, really dry wheat makes for great pasta. “Just so I could make pasta, we built this restaurant,” he jokes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Even before he opened Zinc Bistro 20 years ago, Matt wanted to open an Italian restaurant and explore Italian cuisine.%20http://localhost:4000/whats-on-the-menu-at-the-fat-ox.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Even before he opened Zinc Bistro 20 years ago, Matt wanted to open an Italian restaurant and explore Italian cuisine.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Development took many years, of course, but Matt claims that if he had opened Fat Ox at a different location with a different group, it wouldn’t have the panache that this establishment does. He grew up in the same area and has many memories of eating here, so he refers to Fat Ox’s location as a ‘legacy corner.’ &lt;strong&gt;It’s really a destination restaurant, which is why I was so excited to film this video and showcase it to my clients and anyone visiting Scottsdale.&lt;/strong&gt; The view they have of the outside (see at 3:08) is practically a billboard of our city. Whether you’re traveling, here on business, or dining with family, the Fat Ox checks all the boxes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of, if you’re coming to Scottsdale soon and want to visit the Fat Ox, &lt;strong&gt;Matt suggests getting a Passport Dining card.&lt;/strong&gt; That way you can sample all of his other restaurants and try different cuisines from around the world. This has become a popular option for foodies. You can get French onion soup at Zinc Bistro on a Friday night, hit up Fat Ox the next night and try their homemade pasta, and finish off the weekend with some fresh tacos at The Mission. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many thanks to Matt for letting me interview him in today’s video. If you’d like to know more about the Fat Ox, feel free to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ilovefatox.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;visit their website&lt;/a&gt;. If you have any questions for me, real estate or otherwise, don’t hesitate to call or email me. I’d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 15:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-on-the-menu-at-the-fat-ox.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/whats-on-the-menu-at-the-fat-ox.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Get Your Move On With &quot;Get Your Move On&quot;</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/kh4oe7dgbcc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’ve invited Derek Greene of Get Your Move On to talk a little about his moving company and offer his advice to any homeowners out there facing a move. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Derek started Get Your Move on when he was 24, which makes 2021 their 16th year in business. In that time, he asserts that two things have driven him: &lt;strong&gt;1) never turn down any work, and 2) never leave a customer behind who has a bad taste in their mouth.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That takes work,” Derek says. “We’re not perfect in our industry—nobody is—but we work very very hard, very expeditiously, if there are challenges and issues, to resolve them right away without any questions asked.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get Your Move On is nearly perfect in that regard as far as my past clients’ experiences go, and they were able to help roughly 2,000 families move last year. About 85% of those were residential/local moves, and the other 15% were interstate moves, so they can handle both types of arrangements. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Get Your Move On is nearly perfect in that regard in my past clients’ experiences, and they were able to help roughly 2,000 families move last year.%20http://localhost:4000/get-your-move-on-with-get-your-move-on.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Get Your Move On is nearly perfect in that regard in my past clients’ experiences, and they were able to help roughly 2,000 families move last year.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With so many people buying and selling homes at the same time, there are a lot of simultaneous moves happening out there. When you have a simultaneous close, you’re effectively homeless for four to 48 hours, and &lt;strong&gt;Get Your Move On can store your belongings inside a secure, climate-controlled warehouse overnight, which is very economical. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This way, you don’t have to pay for PODS or other mini-storage options. If you think you’ll need to pursue these options, Derek invites you to give them a call so they can try solving any challenging logistical problems you may have. After that, they’ll give you a quote and let you decide what’s best for your situation. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just like Realtors, there are a lot of moving companies out there. What makes Get Your Move On Different? According to Derek, if your move carries certain challenges, about 90% of all movers there will mishandle them. Half of those, he claims, are rogue movers with malintent. The other half are simply incompetent when it comes to running a small business, which is difficult. The remaining 10% are the ones who do high-level work, and Derek and his company pride themselves on providing high-level service. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It really comes down to having a Nordstrom approach to a customer service problem. Everybody in our company has a core value of humility, and when we do have challenges, we’re not going to start figuring out whose fault it was. We’re just going to solve the problem, and then on the back end, take it as feedback on how to improve our company. I think that’s unique in a service business, as gritty and grimy as the moving business is.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have questions for Derek or would like to speak to him, you can reach him by phone at (480) 695-6621. If you have any real estate needs I can help you with, feel free to call or email me anytime. I’d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 11:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/get-your-move-on-with-get-your-move-on.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/get-your-move-on-with-get-your-move-on.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taking Full Advantage of This Strong Seller’s Market</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0Ugm-S1LqNE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now in Maricopa County, we have about 9,800 units for sale. &lt;strong&gt;Last month, we sold 8,900 units, leaving us with a roughly one-month supply of homes.&lt;/strong&gt; I can confidently say that in my 17 years of selling real estate, this is the hottest seller’s market I’ve ever seen. At the same time, it’s also the most challenging market for buyers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your home is in decent condition and priced reasonably, it &lt;em&gt;will&lt;/em&gt; sell. However, getting the very best price for your home still requires some finesse and expertise. Too often, sellers focus only on price and neglect the importance of selecting an offer that has the best terms overall. We’d advise all sellers to put their homes on the market on Friday and wait till that following Monday to evaluate all offers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Getting the very best price for your home still requires some finesse and expertise.%20http://localhost:4000/taking-full-advantage-of-this-strong-sellers-market.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Getting the very best price for your home still requires some finesse and expertise.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s our job to correspond with buyers’ agents in such a way that promotes bidding wars. We’ll also do everything in our power to get you the best terms. For example, can we remove the appraisal contingency? Can we ask the buyer to purchase your home in as-is condition? Do you want any extra terms? Perhaps you want to stay in the home for another 30 days. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have the leverage to call those shots in this market. We’re here to do what’s best for you. &lt;strong&gt;No two sellers have the same life priorities; whatever’s most important to you, we can make it happen.&lt;/strong&gt; So if you’re curious as to what your home is worth or you’re ready to sell, give us a call or send an email our way. We’d love to help you make the most of this opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 12:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/taking-full-advantage-of-this-strong-sellers-market.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/taking-full-advantage-of-this-strong-sellers-market.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What Nielsen Design Studios Can Do For You</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/TC3vILCrm_o?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m excited to be visiting &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nielsendesignstudios.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Nielsen Design Studios&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; in central Phoenix and speaking with owner Michael Nielsen himself about his business and how he can help you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;His studio has been in business for 35 years, and they offer interior design consulting and products for both residential and commercial properties.&lt;/strong&gt; As you can see in the video, we’re standing right in the middle of their newest product: their outdoor kitchen. According to Michael, this kitchen takes indoor living to the outdoors, and it’s customized to accommodate what the client needs or what their space looks like. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you’re thinking of adding an outdoor kitchen or another neat feature to your home, give Michael a call.%20http://localhost:4000/what-nielsen-design-studios-can-do-for-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you’re thinking of adding an outdoor kitchen or another neat feature to your home, give Michael a call.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many kitchens can you choose from? The possibilities are endless. The style, coloring, configurations, and components are incorporated to fit your needs. With the ‘indoors out’ living environment, kitchens, dining spaces, and poolside lounging areas are all things Nielsen Design Studios can consult you on. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you’re thinking of adding an outdoor kitchen or another neat feature to your home, give Michael a call at (602) 997-6890 or send an email to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:info@nielsendesignstudions.com&quot;&gt;info@nielsendesignstudions.com&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions for me about today’s topic or there are any real estate needs at all that I can assist you with, feel free to reach out to me as well. I’d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 15:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-nielsen-design-studios-can-do-for-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/what-nielsen-design-studios-can-do-for-you.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>3 Tips to Help Buyers Win</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/zS-8sO3jpWI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m here with one of our agents, Melani Beauregard, to discuss ways to win as a buyer in today’s real estate market. It’s a very challenging time to be a buyer or buyer’s agent. There is very little inventory and tons of buyer demand, but Melani has successfully negotiated more than 60 buyer contracts during this difficult period. Here are a few tips to help you win as a buyer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Get pre-approved.&lt;/strong&gt; Pre-qualification isn’t as good as getting pre-approved. Pre-approval means you’re almost completely underwritten, which helps to minimize the close of escrow time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Off-market properties are always a great option for buyers because there’s less competition for them.%20http://localhost:4000/3-tips-to-help-buyers-win.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Off-market properties are always a great option for buyers because there’s less competition for them.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Find the seller’s motivation.&lt;/strong&gt; Have your real estate agent contact the seller’s agent to find out the seller’s motivation. For example, they may want to stay in the home a bit longer to have time to move. If we find out what’s best for the seller, the buyer can use that to get their offer accepted. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. We match buyers to listings when possible.&lt;/strong&gt; On our team, we list many houses, so we try to match our buyers to listings before they even hit the market. Off-market properties are always a great option for buyers because there’s less competition for them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking for an aggressive, proactive, market-intelligent agent who cares about their clients, Melani is the one for you. Reach out to her via phone or email. If you have questions about winning in today’s market or anything else concerning real estate, contact the Monique Walker Team. We would love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 14:26:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-tips-to-help-buyers-win.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/3-tips-to-help-buyers-win.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2020’s Top Real Estate Agent</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/unnamed.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What an amazing honor. Huge thanks and shout-out to my team for making this happen, and to all our awesome clients who trust us with their real estate needs.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through all of the insanity of 2020, real estate agents everywhere were battling to reach new heights to be deemed the Top Real Estate Agent in America. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many fought for the title, but only one could be the best – and for 2020, that agent is Monique Walker of Scottsdale, Arizona. She achieved this title by providing exceptional client experience, flexing her expertise in real estate, and buying and selling the most homes of any of our FastExpert agents in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastexpert.com/blog/2020s-top-real-estate-agent-monique-walker/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Click here to view the full article on FastExpert!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/monique-walker-screenshot-template-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 10:34:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020s-top-real-estate-agent.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020s-top-real-estate-agent.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crystal Ball Predictions for 2021</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/bk2pdDdPce8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m sharing my real estate market predictions for 2021. If I had a crystal ball, I believe I’d see a wonderful market this year due to three factors:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Low inventory.&lt;/strong&gt; We currently have less than one month’s supply of homes, and I foresee that continuing throughout the new year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Demand from California.&lt;/strong&gt; We have high demand in our market, especially from California buyers, and I don’t see that wave letting up anytime soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If I had a crystal ball, I believe I’d see a wonderful market next year.%20http://localhost:4000/crystal-ball-predictions-for-2021.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If I had a crystal ball, I believe I’d see a wonderful market next year.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Low interest rates.&lt;/strong&gt; Our great interest rates drive the market right now; people are getting between 2.5% and 3%, and the Fed has said they won’t raise them for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With all these elements, I think 2021 will be an excellent seller’s market, and we’re eager to get started. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re considering buying, selling, or just have a question about the market, my team and I are here to serve you. Call or email us anytime. We’d love to be your real estate resource.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 16:49:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/crystal-ball-predictions-for-2021.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/crystal-ball-predictions-for-2021.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: Why Consider a Holiday Home Sale?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/m6bPDbtqR68?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many potential home sellers make their plans for the springtime, while others hope for a quick summer sale so they can move while the kids are out of school. It’s often assumed that the fall and winter markets are quieter, if not dead altogether. However, there are numerous advantages to listing your home during the holidays, and today I’m highlighting three major ones: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Buyers who look for a home during the holidays are more serious.&lt;/strong&gt; If they’re pre-approved and willing to use their extra time off work to wiggle around busy holiday schedules and look at homes, they mean business. When it comes to the buyers in our end-of-year market, think quality over quantity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Inventory levels are low.&lt;/strong&gt; Currently, there’s only a one-month supply of homes; fewer options for buyers means more money for you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Job-related relocations are at their peak this time of year.&lt;/strong&gt; People who recently received a huge promotion or found a great new job in a vibrant area (like Phoenix) are rushing to find a home before their official January start date. Again, these types of buyers are just one segment of an exceptionally motivated buyer pool we see every winter. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=When it comes to the buyers in our end-of-year market, think quality over quantity.%20http://localhost:4000/q-why-consider-a-holiday-home-sale.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“When it comes to the buyers in our end-of-year market, think quality over quantity.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Houses show better&lt;/strong&gt; when decorated for the Holidays!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Buyers are more emotional&lt;/strong&gt; during the Holidays, so they are more likely to pay your price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Buyers have more time&lt;/strong&gt; to look for a home during the Holidays than they do during the working week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Some people must buy&lt;/strong&gt; before the end of the year for tax reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;You can sell now for more money and we will provide for a delayed closing&lt;/strong&gt; or extended occupancy until early next year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9. By selling now, you may have the opportunity to be a non-contingent buyer&lt;/strong&gt; during the Spring, when many more houses are on the market for less money! This will allow you to sell high and buy low.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10.&lt;/strong&gt; Since the supply of listings will dramatically increase in January, &lt;strong&gt;there will be less demand for your particular home! Less demand means less money for you!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking about selling soon (perhaps sooner than you’d originally thought in light of this information) and want to know how much your home is worth, I’d love to help you. Just give me a call or send an email anytime! I’m here to serve you. Thank you for all of your support this year, and have a wonderful holiday season!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 15:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-why-consider-a-holiday-home-sale.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-why-consider-a-holiday-home-sale.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Answering 2 More Common Real Estate Questions</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/tz3DkWwgV_M?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m excited to have Troy Peterson of Fidelity National Title Agency join me once again as we continue our real estate Q&amp;amp;A series. Today I’m answering two more important questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The last housing correction was over 10 years ago, aren’t we due for another one?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You would think so. Our market typically cycles every five to seven years, but we’ve been in this one for a decade. Although we’re technically due for a correction, I don’t see one on the horizon based on our current supply and demand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Pricing will continue to go up, but rates won’t stay this low forever.%20http://localhost:4000/answering-2-more-common-real-estate-questions.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Pricing will continue to go up, but rates won’t stay this low forever.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Good investors always sell high and buy low, so why would I want to buy now?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s a really good question. Are you more price-conscious or rate-conscious? Pricing is going to continue to go up over time, even if we have a downward cycle to go through. If you want a low monthly payment on your investment, however, we don’t know how much longer these historically low rates will stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for us about buying, a home, or real estate in general, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 12:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/answering-2-more-common-real-estate-questions.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/answering-2-more-common-real-estate-questions.html</guid>
        
        <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
