<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Phoenix Real Estate Podcast with Monique Walker</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Monique Walker Team - your professional Phoenix Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Monique Walker</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2021-06-21 13:11:24 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Monique Walker</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>Monique@MoniqueSells.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Monique Walker</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Phoenix Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Monique Walker Team - your professional Phoenix Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate 101: How Realtors Help You Sell Your Home</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/real-estate-101-how-realtors-help-you-sell-your-home.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2021-06-17 11:10:47 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Real+Estate+101_+How+Realtors+Help+You+Sell+Your+Home.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Whether you’re young or old, real estate can be a tricky thing to wrap your head around. For many people who are new to the market, it’s often helpful to explain things in the simplest way possible. I like to educate buyers and sellers in a way that’s incredibly easy to grasp — in fact, it’s so straightforward that even kids can understand it.

“Although most of these steps can be a lot more in-depth, this is generally how we progress through the home selling process.”

With the help of my daughter, today I’ll be explaining the seven steps a Realtor takes when helping someone sell their home:


  The seller calls the Realtor.
  The Realtor does a walk-through of the house. A walk-through means going through the home and checking out its features, upgrades, and condition.
  The Realtor determines the price. They usually do this by seeing what similar homes sold for recently.
  The Realtor lists the home on the multiple listing service (MLS). This online platform is where Realtors post a home so that other Realtors and homebuyers can see it.
  The Realtor shows the property to people who want to buy the house.
  The Realtor negotiates with the buyer and their Realtor to find out what they’re willing to pay for the house.
  The home is sold! However, it still takes about 30 days before the sale is completed.


Although most of these steps can be a lot more in-depth, this is generally how we progress through the home selling process. If you have any questions or would like more information about buying or selling a home, feel free to reach out to me. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Real+Estate+101_+How+Realtors+Help+You+Sell+Your+Home.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/uploads/real-estate-101-pod.jpg" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Real+Estate+101_+How+Realtors+Help+You+Sell+Your+Home.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s a simple look at the steps we take when selling a home.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s a simple look at the steps we take when selling a home.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What’s on the Menu at the Fat Ox?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-on-the-menu-at-the-fat-ox.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2021-05-03 15:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/What%E2%80%99s+on+the+Menu+at+the+Fat+Ox_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I’m visiting the Fat Ox restaurant in central Scottsdale to chat with head chef and owner Matt Carter. Located just a few minutes from Old Town Scottsdale and within walking distance of the new Ritz-Carlton being built, the Fat Ox is in one of the most amazing corners you can be in. 

Matt is also the head chef at Zinc Bistro and The Mission. Even before he opened Zinc Bistro 20 years ago, Matt wanted to open an Italian restaurant and explore Italian cuisine and the similar products we have here in Arizona such as figs, olives, and citrus. Additionally, a lot of the wheat that’s grown in Italy is also grown in the Southwest. According to Matt, really dry wheat makes for great pasta. “Just so I could make pasta, we built this restaurant,” he jokes. 

“Even before he opened Zinc Bistro 20 years ago, Matt wanted to open an Italian restaurant and explore Italian cuisine.”

Development took many years, of course, but Matt claims that if he had opened Fat Ox at a different location with a different group, it wouldn’t have the panache that this establishment does. He grew up in the same area and has many memories of eating here, so he refers to Fat Ox’s location as a ‘legacy corner.’ It’s really a destination restaurant, which is why I was so excited to film this video and showcase it to my clients and anyone visiting Scottsdale. The view they have of the outside (see at 3:08) is practically a billboard of our city. Whether you’re traveling, here on business, or dining with family, the Fat Ox checks all the boxes.

Speaking of, if you’re coming to Scottsdale soon and want to visit the Fat Ox, Matt suggests getting a Passport Dining card. That way you can sample all of his other restaurants and try different cuisines from around the world. This has become a popular option for foodies. You can get French onion soup at Zinc Bistro on a Friday night, hit up Fat Ox the next night and try their homemade pasta, and finish off the weekend with some fresh tacos at The Mission. 

Many thanks to Matt for letting me interview him in today’s video. If you’d like to know more about the Fat Ox, feel free to visit their website. If you have any questions for me, real estate or otherwise, don’t hesitate to call or email me. I’d love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/What%E2%80%99s+on+the+Menu+at+the+Fat+Ox_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/What%E2%80%99s+on+the+Menu+at+the+Fat+Ox_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s what you can find at the Fat Ox restaurant here in Scottsdale.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s what you can find at the Fat Ox restaurant here in Scottsdale.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Get Your Move On With "Get Your Move On"</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/get-your-move-on-with-get-your-move-on.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2021-04-13 11:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Get+Your+Move+On+With+Get+Your+Move+On.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I’ve invited Derek Greene of Get Your Move On to talk a little about his moving company and offer his advice to any homeowners out there facing a move. 

Derek started Get Your Move on when he was 24, which makes 2021 their 16th year in business. In that time, he asserts that two things have driven him: 1) never turn down any work, and 2) never leave a customer behind who has a bad taste in their mouth. 

“That takes work,” Derek says. “We’re not perfect in our industry—nobody is—but we work very very hard, very expeditiously, if there are challenges and issues, to resolve them right away without any questions asked.”

Get Your Move On is nearly perfect in that regard as far as my past clients’ experiences go, and they were able to help roughly 2,000 families move last year. About 85% of those were residential/local moves, and the other 15% were interstate moves, so they can handle both types of arrangements. 

“Get Your Move On is nearly perfect in that regard in my past clients’ experiences, and they were able to help roughly 2,000 families move last year.”

With so many people buying and selling homes at the same time, there are a lot of simultaneous moves happening out there. When you have a simultaneous close, you’re effectively homeless for four to 48 hours, and Get Your Move On can store your belongings inside a secure, climate-controlled warehouse overnight, which is very economical. 

This way, you don’t have to pay for PODS or other mini-storage options. If you think you’ll need to pursue these options, Derek invites you to give them a call so they can try solving any challenging logistical problems you may have. After that, they’ll give you a quote and let you decide what’s best for your situation. 

Just like Realtors, there are a lot of moving companies out there. What makes Get Your Move On Different? According to Derek, if your move carries certain challenges, about 90% of all movers there will mishandle them. Half of those, he claims, are rogue movers with malintent. The other half are simply incompetent when it comes to running a small business, which is difficult. The remaining 10% are the ones who do high-level work, and Derek and his company pride themselves on providing high-level service. 

“It really comes down to having a Nordstrom approach to a customer service problem. Everybody in our company has a core value of humility, and when we do have challenges, we’re not going to start figuring out whose fault it was. We’re just going to solve the problem, and then on the back end, take it as feedback on how to improve our company. I think that’s unique in a service business, as gritty and grimy as the moving business is.” 

If you have questions for Derek or would like to speak to him, you can reach him by phone at (480) 695-6621. If you have any real estate needs I can help you with, feel free to call or email me anytime. I’d love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Get+Your+Move+On+With+Get+Your+Move+On.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Get+Your+Move+On+With+Get+Your+Move+On.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Derek Greene has some thoughts on the moving process you need to hear.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Derek Greene has some thoughts on the moving process you need to hear.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Taking Full Advantage of This Strong Seller’s Market</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/taking-full-advantage-of-this-strong-sellers-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2021-03-30 12:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Taking+Full+Advantage+of+This+Strong+Seller%E2%80%99s+Market.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Right now in Maricopa County, we have about 9,800 units for sale. Last month, we sold 8,900 units, leaving us with a roughly one-month supply of homes. I can confidently say that in my 17 years of selling real estate, this is the hottest seller’s market I’ve ever seen. At the same time, it’s also the most challenging market for buyers. 

If your home is in decent condition and priced reasonably, it will sell. However, getting the very best price for your home still requires some finesse and expertise. Too often, sellers focus only on price and neglect the importance of selecting an offer that has the best terms overall. We’d advise all sellers to put their homes on the market on Friday and wait till that following Monday to evaluate all offers. 

“Getting the very best price for your home still requires some finesse and expertise.”

It’s our job to correspond with buyers’ agents in such a way that promotes bidding wars. We’ll also do everything in our power to get you the best terms. For example, can we remove the appraisal contingency? Can we ask the buyer to purchase your home in as-is condition? Do you want any extra terms? Perhaps you want to stay in the home for another 30 days. 

We have the leverage to call those shots in this market. We’re here to do what’s best for you. No two sellers have the same life priorities; whatever’s most important to you, we can make it happen. So if you’re curious as to what your home is worth or you’re ready to sell, give us a call or send an email our way. We’d love to help you make the most of this opportunity.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Taking+Full+Advantage+of+This+Strong+Seller%E2%80%99s+Market.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Taking+Full+Advantage+of+This+Strong+Seller%E2%80%99s+Market.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here is how we’ve positioned ourselves to help you maximize your sale.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here is how we’ve positioned ourselves to help you maximize your sale.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Nielsen Design Studios Can Do For You</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-nielsen-design-studios-can-do-for-you.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2021-03-12 15:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/What+Nielsen+Design+Studios+Can+Do+For+You.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I’m excited to be visiting Nielsen Design Studios in central Phoenix and speaking with owner Michael Nielsen himself about his business and how he can help you. 

His studio has been in business for 35 years, and they offer interior design consulting and products for both residential and commercial properties. As you can see in the video, we’re standing right in the middle of their newest product: their outdoor kitchen. According to Michael, this kitchen takes indoor living to the outdoors, and it’s customized to accommodate what the client needs or what their space looks like. 

“If you’re thinking of adding an outdoor kitchen or another neat feature to your home, give Michael a call.”

How many kitchens can you choose from? The possibilities are endless. The style, coloring, configurations, and components are incorporated to fit your needs. With the ‘indoors out’ living environment, kitchens, dining spaces, and poolside lounging areas are all things Nielsen Design Studios can consult you on. 

So if you’re thinking of adding an outdoor kitchen or another neat feature to your home, give Michael a call at (602) 997-6890 or send an email to info@nielsendesignstudions.com. If you have questions for me about today’s topic or there are any real estate needs at all that I can assist you with, feel free to reach out to me as well. I’d love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/What+Nielsen+Design+Studios+Can+Do+For+You.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/What+Nielsen+Design+Studios+Can+Do+For+You.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Nielsen Design Studios has been in business for 35 years. Here’s why.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Nielsen Design Studios has been in business for 35 years. Here’s why.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Tips to Help Buyers Win</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-tips-to-help-buyers-win.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2021-02-10 14:26:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Today I’m here with one of our agents, Melani Beauregard, to discuss ways to win as a buyer in today’s real estate market. It’s a very challenging time to be a buyer or buyer’s agent. There is very little inventory and tons of buyer demand, but Melani has successfully negotiated more than 60 buyer contracts during this difficult period. Here are a few tips to help you win as a buyer:

1. Get pre-approved. Pre-qualification isn’t as good as getting pre-approved. Pre-approval means you’re almost completely underwritten, which helps to minimize the close of escrow time.

“Off-market properties are always a great option for buyers because there’s less competition for them.”

2. Find the seller’s motivation. Have your real estate agent contact the seller’s agent to find out the seller’s motivation. For example, they may want to stay in the home a bit longer to have time to move. If we find out what’s best for the seller, the buyer can use that to get their offer accepted. 

3. We match buyers to listings when possible. On our team, we list many houses, so we try to match our buyers to listings before they even hit the market. Off-market properties are always a great option for buyers because there’s less competition for them. 

If you’re looking for an aggressive, proactive, market-intelligent agent who cares about their clients, Melani is the one for you. Reach out to her via phone or email. If you have questions about winning in today’s market or anything else concerning real estate, contact the Monique Walker Team. We would love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are three tips to help buyers win in today’s challenging market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are three tips to help buyers win in today’s challenging market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>2020’s Top Real Estate Agent</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020s-top-real-estate-agent.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2021-02-09 10:34:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

What an amazing honor. Huge thanks and shout-out to my team for making this happen, and to all our awesome clients who trust us with their real estate needs.

Through all of the insanity of 2020, real estate agents everywhere were battling to reach new heights to be deemed the Top Real Estate Agent in America. 

Many fought for the title, but only one could be the best – and for 2020, that agent is Monique Walker of Scottsdale, Arizona. She achieved this title by providing exceptional client experience, flexing her expertise in real estate, and buying and selling the most homes of any of our FastExpert agents in 2020.

Click here to view the full article on FastExpert!


</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We are over the moon excited about earning the Fast Expert #1 Agent in the US!</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We are over the moon excited about earning the Fast Expert #1 Agent in the US!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Crystal Ball Predictions for 2021</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/crystal-ball-predictions-for-2021.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2021-01-08 16:49:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Crystal+Ball+Predictions+for+2021.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I’m sharing my real estate market predictions for 2021. If I had a crystal ball, I believe I’d see a wonderful market this year due to three factors:

1. Low inventory. We currently have less than one month’s supply of homes, and I foresee that continuing throughout the new year.

2. Demand from California. We have high demand in our market, especially from California buyers, and I don’t see that wave letting up anytime soon.

“If I had a crystal ball, I believe I’d see a wonderful market next year.”

3. Low interest rates. Our great interest rates drive the market right now; people are getting between 2.5% and 3%, and the Fed has said they won’t raise them for a while.

With all these elements, I think 2021 will be an excellent seller’s market, and we’re eager to get started. 

If you’re considering buying, selling, or just have a question about the market, my team and I are here to serve you. Call or email us anytime. We’d love to be your real estate resource.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Crystal+Ball+Predictions+for+2021.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Crystal+Ball+Predictions+for+2021.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>If I had a crystal ball to gaze into, here’s what I think I’d see for 2021.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>If I had a crystal ball to gaze into, here’s what I think I’d see for 2021.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Q: Why Consider a Holiday Home Sale?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-why-consider-a-holiday-home-sale.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-12-22 15:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Q_+Why+Consider+a+Holiday+Home+Sale_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Many potential home sellers make their plans for the springtime, while others hope for a quick summer sale so they can move while the kids are out of school. It’s often assumed that the fall and winter markets are quieter, if not dead altogether. However, there are numerous advantages to listing your home during the holidays, and today I’m highlighting three major ones: 

1. Buyers who look for a home during the holidays are more serious. If they’re pre-approved and willing to use their extra time off work to wiggle around busy holiday schedules and look at homes, they mean business. When it comes to the buyers in our end-of-year market, think quality over quantity. 

2. Inventory levels are low. Currently, there’s only a one-month supply of homes; fewer options for buyers means more money for you. 

3. Job-related relocations are at their peak this time of year. People who recently received a huge promotion or found a great new job in a vibrant area (like Phoenix) are rushing to find a home before their official January start date. Again, these types of buyers are just one segment of an exceptionally motivated buyer pool we see every winter. 

“When it comes to the buyers in our end-of-year market, think quality over quantity.”

4. Houses show better when decorated for the Holidays!

5. Buyers are more emotional during the Holidays, so they are more likely to pay your price.

6. Buyers have more time to look for a home during the Holidays than they do during the working week.

7. Some people must buy before the end of the year for tax reasons.

8. You can sell now for more money and we will provide for a delayed closing or extended occupancy until early next year!

9. By selling now, you may have the opportunity to be a non-contingent buyer during the Spring, when many more houses are on the market for less money! This will allow you to sell high and buy low.

10. Since the supply of listings will dramatically increase in January, there will be less demand for your particular home! Less demand means less money for you!

If you’re thinking about selling soon (perhaps sooner than you’d originally thought in light of this information) and want to know how much your home is worth, I’d love to help you. Just give me a call or send an email anytime! I’m here to serve you. Thank you for all of your support this year, and have a wonderful holiday season!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Q_+Why+Consider+a+Holiday+Home+Sale_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Q_+Why+Consider+a+Holiday+Home+Sale_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are three ways sellers who list during the holidays have an advantage.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are three ways sellers who list during the holidays have an advantage.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Answering 2 More Common Real Estate Questions</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/answering-2-more-common-real-estate-questions.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-12-07 12:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/Answering+2+More+Common+Real+Estate+Questions.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I’m excited to have Troy Peterson of Fidelity National Title Agency join me once again as we continue our real estate Q&amp;A series. Today I’m answering two more important questions.

“The last housing correction was over 10 years ago, aren’t we due for another one?”

You would think so. Our market typically cycles every five to seven years, but we’ve been in this one for a decade. Although we’re technically due for a correction, I don’t see one on the horizon based on our current supply and demand.

“Pricing will continue to go up, but rates won’t stay this low forever.”

“Good investors always sell high and buy low, so why would I want to buy now?”

That’s a really good question. Are you more price-conscious or rate-conscious? Pricing is going to continue to go up over time, even if we have a downward cycle to go through. If you want a low monthly payment on your investment, however, we don’t know how much longer these historically low rates will stay.

If you have any questions for us about buying, a home, or real estate in general, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/Answering+2+More+Common+Real+Estate+Questions.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/Answering+2+More+Common+Real+Estate+Questions.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I’m back with Troy Peterson to answer more of your important questions.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I’m back with Troy Peterson to answer more of your important questions.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Q: Why Is It Harder to Be a Buyer Right Now?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-why-is-it-harder-to-be-a-buyer-right-now.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-10-26 14:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Q%3A+Why+Is+It+Harder+to+Be+a+Buyer+Right+Now%3F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I’m joined by Troy Peterson from the Fidelity National Title Agency, who has helped me compile a list of great questions that consumers have been asking him about real estate. Together, we’re tackling another question so you have a better understanding of the process.

“I hear about all the growth and construction in Phoenix, so why is it so hard to find a house right now and get my offer accepted?’

It is very difficult to be a buyer in this market, and that means you have to hire a very aggressive, knowledgeable, proactive buyer’s agent to help you. We have the lowest number of homes for sale that we’ve had in nearly a decade, which makes the market hyper-competitive. You can sell your property for a super high price, but that means you’ll also have to purchase your new home for a super high price.

“You have to sell high and buy high in this market.”

The ultimate question for potential buyers to answer is, “Are you in it for the short game or the long game?” We’ll probably go through another market cycle sometime in the next five to seven years, so if you sell high, buy high, and plan to stay in the home for about that long, then you’ll see solid appreciation on an asset you can enjoy every single day. If you’re only planning to stay in it for a year or so, it might not be the best idea financially to purchase.

If you’re curious about what your home is worth or if you’re looking to buy a home, my team and I would love to help. Feel free to give us a call, text, or email! We’re here to serve you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Q%3A+Why+Is+It+Harder+to+Be+a+Buyer+Right+Now%3F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Q%3A+Why+Is+It+Harder+to+Be+a+Buyer+Right+Now%3F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Troy Peterson from Fidelity Title is here today to help me answer some more great consumer questions.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Troy Peterson from Fidelity Title is here today to help me answer some more great consumer questions.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Answering Your Top Real Estate Questions</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/answering-your-top-real-estate-questions.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-10-09 14:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Answering+Your+Top+Real+Estate+Questions.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I’m joined by Troy Peterson from the Fidelity National Title Agency, who has helped me compile a list of great questions that consumers have been asking him about real estate. Together, we’ll tackle these questions so that you have a better understanding of the process.

“I’ve heard that homes are selling fast and for more than the asking price. Why do I need a Realtor to help me sell my home when I could just pocket that money?”

Yes, you could sell your home on your own, but the benefit of a Realtor is that we can generate multiple offers for your listing. That leads to competition among buyers, which in turn can lead to you receiving much more than your asking price. A Realtor can net you the most money, especially in a competitive market. More than price, we also help you get the best terms.

“I always lean toward pricing a home correctly at fair market value and being more aggressive with our marketing.”

“If homes are selling for over asking price, then shouldn’t I put my house on the market at a really high price and only come down if I needed?”

That certainly is a strategy. I usually tell my sellers that they have two options. List it at market value, generate multiple offers, and then get top dollar when it does sell; or list it higher than market value and get fewer showings, which will usually only help your competition. So you need to decide if you want to help your competition or if you want to get more exposure for your listing. I always lean toward pricing it correctly at fair market value and being more aggressive with our marketing so that we can get as many eyes on your homes as possible.

If you’re curious about what your home is worth or you’re looking to buy a home, the Monique Walker Team would love to help you. Don’t hesitate to reach out to us! We’re here to serve you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Answering+Your+Top+Real+Estate+Questions.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Answering+Your+Top+Real+Estate+Questions.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Troy Peterson from Fidelity Title is here today to help me answer some great consumer questions.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Troy Peterson from Fidelity Title is here today to help me answer some great consumer questions.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Q: What’s Going on in Our Market Right Now?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-whats-going-on-in-our-market-right-now.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-09-25 16:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Q-+Whats+Going+on+in+Our+Market+Right+Now_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

It’s no longer a secret that our market is on fire and performing well at every price point. Whether you’re at the $200,000 price point or the $2 million price point, it’s a hyper seller’s market all the same. Here are the latest stats to prove it: 

Last month, we had a 1.24 months’ supply of homes (that’s the amount of time it would take to sell all existing homes on the market if no new ones were to list). At this time last year, we had a 1.74 months’ supply of homes, so clearly we’re working with fewer homes in this current market. 

9,200 homes sold in August 2020, whereas 8,900 sold in August 2019. Despite a decrease in available homes, demand has remained sky-high, creating favorable conditions for sellers. If you’re curious to find out what your home is worth, I’d love to help; give me a call or send an email my way. We’re always here to serve!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Q-+Whats+Going+on+in+Our+Market+Right+Now_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Q-+Whats+Going+on+in+Our+Market+Right+Now_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are the latest news and notes on our market as we welcome fall.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are the latest news and notes on our market as we welcome fall.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>An Interview With Our Awesome Buyer’s Agent</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/an-interview-with-our-awesome-buyers-agent.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-08-11 12:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/An+Interview+With+Our+Awesome+Buyers+Agent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I’m joined by Melani Beauregard, one of the Monique Walker Team’s awesome buyer agents, for an interview about her growth since joining our team. 

Melani’s been in the real estate business for four years. In her first year, she closed fewer than 25 homes, but in her third year (after she joined us), she helped 48 families buy a home. Of course, our job isn’t just about closing deals; it’s about helping people. That’s why her goal for 2020 is to help 70 families buy a home. 

As of the recording of this video, she has 32 closings to her name, along with 10 pendings. Our team doesn’t like to be normal, and those numbers aren’t normal—albeit in a very good way. 

How did she double her production?

“Well, I have a mindset that I decided I was going to surround myself with other successful people like yourself,” she says, “And I was very blessed to be invited to join your team. So, I feel like being around other people that are in the business and constantly reminding myself that I don’t know everything and that there’s always room to grow. And then just taking each experience that I’ve had and learn from it wholeheartedly. And then just constantly wanting to have the best for my clients.” 

“We need someone who matches our drive, hustle, and enthusiasm, so if you’re interested in filling this position, don’t hesitate to call me today.”

In the two-and-a-half years Melani has been with us, she’s been able to identify our strengths in the form of a list she titled “What Being on the Monique Walker Team Means to Me.” These strengths include, in her words:


  Having positive influences
  Accountability 
  Strong integrity
  Professional and experienced staff 
  Consistent lead flow (“There’s so much to go around I can’t to it all by myself.”)
  Achieving my goals
  Endless coaching 
  Striving to always by my best 
  A fun, positive environment
  Financial freedom 
  I’m so busy I don’t have time to do my nails 😄


For any agent who’s looking to join a team and needs a little more support, I think it’s a powerful message for them to know that they can do more—they just need the right environment. If anything Melani mentioned today struck a chord with you and you want to achieve the same growth in your career, you can because we’re looking for another agent to join our team. 

As Melani said, she can’t handle all of the leads herself. We need someone who matches our drive, hustle, and enthusiasm, so if you’re interested in filling this position, don’t hesitate to call me today. I’d love to speak with you. 

As always, if you have any other questions, feel free to reach out to me as well. I’m here to help.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/An+Interview+With+Our+Awesome+Buyers+Agent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/An+Interview+With+Our+Awesome+Buyers+Agent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s what Melani Beauregard has to say about being on our team.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s what Melani Beauregard has to say about being on our team.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Q: Who Is The Monique Walker Team?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-who-is-the-monique-walker-team.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-07-29 15:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Q-+Who+Is+the+Monique+Walker+Team_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Who exactly is The Monique Walker Team? It’s a group of amazing professionals that are completely dedicated to serving our clients.

About 10 years ago, I had an epiphany about our business. I never want our clients to wait on me. I want our clients to feel like they are waited on. So who are these amazing team members?

First, we have buyer’s agent Melanie Beauregard, who helps me prospect for buyers and helped 50 buyers herself last year.

Next, we have our listing coordinator, Monica Mendoza. She’s our concierge for our sellers and my right-hand gal when it comes to marketing.

“Our team was created to serve you at the highest level.”

Shannon Newell is our transaction coordinator. She dots the i’s, crosses the t’s, and makes sure we get to the finish line with a smooth transaction.

Behind the scenes, we have Diann Barker, Sara Baker, and my husband, who is our operations manager.

I created this team for our clients and to be able to give them smooth transactions. Our team was created to serve you at the highest level, and our goal is to help you get the best price in the quickest amount of time.

If you have any questions for me, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Q-+Who+Is+the+Monique+Walker+Team_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Q-+Who+Is+the+Monique+Walker+Team_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today I’m going to introduce you to my fantastic team.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today I’m going to introduce you to my fantastic team.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Youth Sports Programs With Arizona Athletics</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/youth-sports-programs-with-arizona-athletics.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-07-13 10:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Youth+Sports+Programs+With+Arizona+Athletics.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Everybody is looking for a way to get out and be active this summer, and my friends Elijah and Taylor joined me recently to talk about Arizona Athletics and their 2020 sports programs for kids.

Elijah is the President of Arizona Athletics. This summer, they’re holding basketball camps every Monday, Tuesday, and Wednesday from 10:30 a.m. to 1:30 p.m. The camps are limited to 24 kids in a nice, big gym. They don’t social distance through the entire camp due to the nature of the game, but they do have temperature checks at the door, frequent hand washing, and limit distance as much as possible. If you’re not comfortable with that, they are also offering at-home and private training.

The volleyball camps are taking all the same precautions with limited contact. Again, there are some times during the camp where social distancing is not possible, so they are offering at-home training and private training as well.

“They also offer small group and private lessons for more advanced campers.”

The basketball camps are for those in grades four through eight. It’s an intermediate camp, so beginners might have a tougher time. For the really advanced seventh and eighth grade campers, they recommend the private advanced lessons.

The volleyball camps are for those in grades three through eight, and they welcome players of all levels. For those who are a little more advanced, they also have small group and private training.

You can find Arizona Athletics and their Youth Sports Programs at Archway Cicero, off the 1010 and Talking Stick exit.

If you have any questions about Arizona Athletics and their sports programs, you can reach out to them on their website.

If you have any other questions for me or any real estate needs that I can assist with, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Youth+Sports+Programs+With+Arizona+Athletics.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Youth+Sports+Programs+With+Arizona+Athletics.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Arizona Athletics is holding basketball and volleyball camps all summer.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Arizona Athletics is holding basketball and volleyball camps all summer.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>June 2020 Market Update</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/june-2020-market-update.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-06-30 15:37:37 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/June+2020+Market+Update.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We are still in a great seller’s market here in Phoenix; we have very little inventory and tons of demand. We only have a 2.2-month supply of homes. Last month we had buyers from Chicago, Minneapolis, and California purchase our listings, as well as people within our city. 

People are attracted to Arizona because of our home prices, spread-out land, low cost of living, and wonderful interest rates between 3% and 3.5%. Though sales are still down about 30%, it’s because of our low inventory. We can help you safely buy or sell, even amid the pandemic. 

If you have questions about what your home may be worth or anything else concerning real estate, call, text, or email us. We’re here to help.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/June+2020+Market+Update.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/June+2020+Market+Update.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s where our real estate market stands as we head into July.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s where our real estate market stands as we head into July.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Reverse Mortgages Work</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-reverse-mortgages-work.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-05-11 14:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/How+Reverse+Mortgages+Work.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Reverse mortgages are for homeowners who are at least 62 years old, have accrued a decent amount of equity (roughly 50%), and don’t want to have a mortgage payment for the rest of their lives. 

A reverse mortgage is a fairly complex product that warrants an in-depth conversation with your financial advisor. It’s geared for fixed-income individuals who want to stay in their homes while alleviating the burden of monthly mortgage payments. It’s also advocated by financial planners whenever there’s a downturn in the stock markets and their clients don’t want to liquidate their assets; a reverse mortgage allows them to free up a cash pool and avoid pulling money out of stocks or bonds. 

“A reverse mortgage is a fairly complex product that warrants an in-depth conversation with your financial advisor.”

Essentially, a reverse mortgage gets paid off just like any conventional mortgage would, though it’s structured differently. If, for example, a son or daughter finds themselves needing to sell the property of a deceased parent who had a reverse mortgage, they will have 12 months from the parent’s passing to sell the property. Since a reverse mortgage loan is not to exceed the home’s value, the proceeds from the sale of the property will pay off the loan. 

Bay Equity Home Loans has several reverse mortgages specialists ready to answer your questions and explore whether taking out a reverse mortgage is right for you. Call Tom Ross at 602-791-5861 or email him at tross@bayeq.com. If you have any real estate-related questions, please don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’re always here to help!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/How+Reverse+Mortgages+Work.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/How+Reverse+Mortgages+Work.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Tom Ross of Bay Equity joins me today to discuss the requirements and benefits of a reverse mortgage.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Tom Ross of Bay Equity joins me today to discuss the requirements and benefits of a reverse mortgage.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Your March 2020 Market Update</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/your-march-2020-market-update.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-04-28 14:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Your+March+2020+Market+Update.mp4</guid>
        <description>

What do the latest numbers say about our Phoenix market? Here’s how the numbers from March compare with those from March 2019. 

The number of sales was identical, but inventory dropped 35%. What does this mean if you’re a seller? With just 1.6 months’ worth of homes, there aren’t a lot of properties out there. Even amid the pandemic, buyers are still buying homes. 

“With just 1.6 months’ worth of homes, there aren’t a lot of properties out there.”

It’s also interesting to note that 83% of all homes under construction are below the $500,000 mark. This means that that market is very speedy, while the higher-end market is slowing down a bit. There’s still a lot of demand, but some buyers (especially Midwesterners and Californians) are sitting on the sidelines because, obviously, they aren’t able to come down here. 

It will be a very exciting time once the pandemic subsides—our market is holding steady. 

If you’d like to know your home’s value or what’s happening in your local area, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’m here to help.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Your+March+2020+Market+Update.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Your+March+2020+Market+Update.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>According to the latest numbers, our market is holding steady amid the pandemic.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>According to the latest numbers, our market is holding steady amid the pandemic.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why Now Is a Good Time to List Your Home</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-now-is-a-good-time-to-list-your-home.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-04-08 15:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Why+Now+Is+a+Good+Time+to+List+Your+Home.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Our team is staying safe and healthy, and I hope you and your family are as well. My goal today is to share some facts with you that point to now being a surprisingly good time to list: 

1. Inventory levels are incredibly low. We already had low levels before this health crisis, but since some people are taking their homes off of the market now, listing yours will make it one of a select few options for buyers. 

2. Buyers are serious. Unless they absolutely need to purchase a home, you’d expect buyers to stay on the sidelines and wait for more normal circumstances to return. While you will have fewer showings if you list now, the quality of those showings will be higher than usual because only the most motivated buyers will be looking at your home. 

“Now is a surprisingly great time to list your home.”

3. Interest rates are very low. Though buying and selling require creativity right now, some buyers feel it’s worth it to capitalize on these rates. 

4. More online searches are happening now than ever before. Buyers have more time than usual to search for homes online, and the impressions are up by 10x. Your home could appear in countless searches!

Though the health crisis news is grim, the real estate industry is fortunate in the sense that the market is holding up quite well. 

If you have any questions about what was discussed today, or if you’re interested in buying or selling a home soon but aren’t sure how to proceed in these times, reach out to us. Call, email, set up a Zoom meeting—whatever method works best, we’re always here to help.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Why+Now+Is+a+Good+Time+to+List+Your+Home.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Why+Now+Is+a+Good+Time+to+List+Your+Home.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Fear, doubt, and intuition may tell sellers to wait until normality returns, but the market facts paint a different picture. Here’s what I mean.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Fear, doubt, and intuition may tell sellers to wait until normality returns, but the market facts paint a different picture. Here’s what I mean.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>An Update on the Phoenix Real Estate Market</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/an-update-on-the-phoenix-real-estate-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-04-06 11:28:33 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/An+Update+on+the+Phoenix+Real+Estate+Market.mp4</guid>
        <description>

The spring market has begun here in Phoenix, even amidst a global pandemic. I’m here today to deliver facts and dispel some myths about what you think the real estate market might be doing. Here in Maricopa County, sales actually went up from 500 on March 18 to 832 on March 25 and over 700 by March 31. Our governor has deemed real estate an essential business, and fortunately we haven’t been hit as hard as other states have.

If you have any questions about what I discussed in this video, or if you’re interested in buying or selling a home soon but aren’t sure how to proceed in these times, reach out to us. We’re always here to help and look forward to touching base with you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/An+Update+on+the+Phoenix+Real+Estate+Market.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/An+Update+on+the+Phoenix+Real+Estate+Market.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>A lot of people have been asking me about the real estate market and how things are going during this global crisis. Here’s what you need to know.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>A lot of people have been asking me about the real estate market and how things are going during this global crisis. Here’s what you need to know.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Answering Google’s Real Estate FAQs</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/answering-googles-real-estate-faqs.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-24 14:45:04 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Answering+Googles+Real+Estate+FAQs.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Online consumers frequently have questions about various aspects of the real estate process. Today, Tom Ross of Bay Equity joins me to help answer some of the internet’s most frequently asked questions so consumers can feel confident as they think about starting their own transactions.

Feel free to follow along in the video above, or use the timestamps below to navigate the video at your leisure:

0:30—Is “real estate agent” capitalized?1:13—Are real estate agents overpaid?1:28—Why do real estate agents do open houses?2:42—Are real estate agents worth it?3:39—Can agents have tattoos?4:02—Can agents talk about schools?4:27—Can real estate agents originate mortgage loans?6:02—Are real estate agents rich?6:40—What do agents do all day?

If you ever have any more questions about real estate, don’t hesitate to reach out to us! We’d love to be of value to you, so just let us know what we can do to help.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Answering+Googles+Real+Estate+FAQs.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Answering+Googles+Real+Estate+FAQs.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today I’m here with my favorite lender, Tom Ross from Bay Equity, to answer some of the most frequently asked questions about real estate on the internet.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today I’m here with my favorite lender, Tom Ross from Bay Equity, to answer some of the most frequently asked questions about real estate on the internet.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Home Improvement Tips for 2020 Sellers</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/home-improvement-tips-for-2020-sellers.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-09 15:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Receive+a+Free+Market+Snapshot.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Every home seller wants top dollar for their property, so many turn to making updates and upgrades to their home in order to maximize its value.

Typically, money is better spent inside the home versus outside, so you may want to wait on fixing up the driveway or investing in a newer fence, for example. 

Truly, the rooms that should be your focus are the kitchen and bathrooms. Buyers are searching for turnkey properties that will involve as little hassle as possible. Ideally, they want to just hand over their down payment and mortgage and move right into the home.

Whenever we put up a new construction home for sale, or a home that’s already been renovated, it’s always an easier sale than trying to market a home that’s been neglected. 

“If you’re needing home improvements, start with the kitchen.”

If you’re needing home improvements, deal with the kitchen first. This is where families spend the most time; it’s hard to imagine celebrating a holiday without all your relatives mingling in a kitchen as they load up on food. Generally, buyers love an open concept where the living room flows into a modernized kitchen with an island as a focal point. 

Kitchen renovations can be costly and extensive, so it’s no wonder buyers prefer properties where all the heavy lifting of remodeling has already been done and the kitchen is up-to-date and stylish. 

When it comes to bathrooms, you want them light, bright, and uncluttered. Design-wise, think modern, fresh, and sleek. This is the second most impactful renovation you can make. 

If you’re thinking about painting the interior, stop thinking and just do it! You can’t go wrong; you’ll get a 150% return on your investment, as painting is the cheapest way to make your home feel fresh and new. Buyers will see the value right away. 

If you have additional questions about the information covered in today’s message, feel free to call or email me. I would love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Receive+a+Free+Market+Snapshot.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Receive+a+Free+Market+Snapshot.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s my advice on how to get the best return on your investment when it comes to updating your home for the market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s my advice on how to get the best return on your investment when it comes to updating your home for the market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Receive a Free Market Snapshot</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/receive-a-free-market-snapshot.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-02-11 14:01:56 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Receive+a+Free+Market+Snapshot.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Would you like to know what your home is worth? Today we’re going to discuss a free service I offer called a market snapshot. If you want to know what your home is worth, have a rental property you want to keep updated on, or you know where you want to move and wish to keep track of that specific area, I have a simple tool that can help. 

Click here to receive a specific market snapshot. Simply input your information, and then you can get a report of that zip code. This is not an accurate home value report to know exactly what your home is worth, but it gives you an idea of what’s happening in that area. If you want to know what the list-to-sales price ratio is, how long it’s taking homes to sell, what new properties have come onto the market, and so on, that’s the kind of data you’ll receive from a market snapshot. 

For a completely accurate value of your home, you can call or email me directly. Also, feel free to reach out to me with any questions about the market snapshot or real estate in general. I would love to help you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Receive+a+Free+Market+Snapshot.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Receive+a+Free+Market+Snapshot.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I’m sharing a free tool I provide that can help you get information about a specific area: the market snapshot.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I’m sharing a free tool I provide that can help you get information about a specific area: the market snapshot.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What's the Best Season to Sell?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-the-best-season-to-sell.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2020-01-27 14:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/What's+the+Best+Season+to+Sell%3F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

When is the best time to sell? I looked at last year’s data for Maricopa County and saw that most sales took place in May—more than 10,000, to be exact. It’s currently taking 60 days on average for a home on the MLS to go under contract, so to close in May, you’d want to list your home in March. 

To answer the question more directly: The best time to put a home on the market is when you’ve decluttered, repainted, shampooed the carpets, staged the property, and done everything else that’s needed to get it ready for the market. 

We’re in a strong seller’s market, so the sooner you prepare your house the better! For data on your personal property and to know your home value, please reach out to me. I’m always happy to receive your call or email.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/What's+the+Best+Season+to+Sell%3F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/What's+the+Best+Season+to+Sell%3F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s my tip for timing your sale in our Maricopa County market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s my tip for timing your sale in our Maricopa County market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Should You Work With an iBuyer?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/should-you-work-with-an-ibuyer.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2019-12-03 16:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Should+You+Work+With+an+iBuyer_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Should you work with or consider an offer from an iBuyer?

iBuyers are also known as internet buyers or instant buyers. The iBuyers of today’s market are companies like Zillow, Opendoor, Offerpad, and several other prominent names. Since I’ve worked with most of them, here are some things to consider when contemplating whether to work with iBuyers:

iBuyers are so enticing because they will bring you a cash offer. Often they will close within a three- to four-week period or sooner. They may purchase the property in as-is condition. So the convenience of those offers is an extra value. 

However, these companies are usually purchasing properties between 10% to 20% under market value. So when you work with an iBuyer you will not net the most money off of your home sale. 

“Allow me to do the free due diligence for you.”

Many of my clients call and say they’re considering this offer, and I am glad to go on the MLS for you, look at the property, and see what we can list and sell it for. I’ve done this hundreds of times. I’ll look at commissions, inspections, and how much you’ll net if you work with me compared to an iBuyer. Often I’m seeing that we’re able to net clients anywhere between $10,000 to $25,000 thousand more selling it though me as opposed to the iBuyer. 

Don’t be too hasty to take those quick offers, do your due diligence. If it makes sense, I will let you know to go ahead and move forward with those iBuyers. But allow me to do the free due diligence for you first. 

If you would like me to look over an iBuyer’s offer or you have any other questions, email or call me, I would be happy to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Should+You+Work+With+an+iBuyer_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Should+You+Work+With+an+iBuyer_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I’m sharing my tips for how to determine whether you should work with an iBuyer.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I’m sharing my tips for how to determine whether you should work with an iBuyer.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Let Us Help Connect You</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/let-us-help-connect-you.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2019-11-21 15:11:07 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Today I’m coming to you live from an exclusive RE/MAX conference in Washington DC to share a friendly reminder: If you’re looking to buy or sell a home outside of Maricopa County, my team and I can connect you with real estate agents from all across the country. If you need help with any real estate needs anywhere in the US or Canada, just give me a call and I’d love to help you. To see my full message, watch this short video. 

As always, if you have any other real estate questions or concerns regarding our Phoenix market, don’t hesitate to reach out to me as well. I’d be happy to speak with you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Description: In addition to buying or selling within Maricopa County, we can also connect you with any agent anywhere in the US or Canada.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Description: In addition to buying or selling within Maricopa County, we can also connect you with any agent anywhere in the US or Canada.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>11 Reasons to List During the Holiday Season</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/11-reasons-to-list-during-the-holiday-season.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2019-10-27 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>
</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>
</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What’s Going on in Our Market?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/whats-going-on-in-our-market.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2019-10-11 16:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Whats+Going+on+in+Our+Market_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Folks, our market is on fire. We are in such a strong seller’s market, and we’ve already had a phenomenal month. Here are the details:

Though our level of inventory is low, demand for homes is very high. We have 1.75 months’ worth of available inventory. This same time last year, we had 2.15 months of supply, so we’re slightly stronger this year.

“Our market is on fire.”

To give you an example that will help clarify what this means, we just listed a property in North Scottsdale for $875,000, and we were able to sell it in about a week and a half for $860,000. We listed another property in North Phoenix for $435,000, and we were able to get the sellers that price when it sold. Another property we listed at $270,000 had 20 offers on it, and we were able to sell it for $280,000.

In the end, for all price points under $1 million, the market is really strong. If you’re thinking about selling your house or if you’re just curious about the value of your home, please reach out to me. I’d be so happy to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Whats+Going+on+in+Our+Market_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Whats+Going+on+in+Our+Market_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s your Fall 2019 real estate market update.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s your Fall 2019 real estate market update.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Join Us for the 2019 Battle of the Sexes</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/join-us-for-the-2019-battle-of-the-sexes.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2019-10-01 05:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Join+Us+for+the+2019+Battle+of+the+Sexes.mp4</guid>
        <description>

The Battle of the Sexes 2019 is almost here! There will be food, drinks, a raffle, and music. There will be plenty of fun for the whole family. 

Join us on November 2 at the Phoenician Resort (6000 E Camelback Road) from 1 p.m. to 4 p.m. This is a free event to people of all ages and we’d love to see you there.

“We’ve raised enough money through this event to help over 40,000 people.”

In the past, we’ve raised enough through this event in 12 years to help over 40,000 people. It’s my 10th year playing, and I’m so excited to play this year and raise even more money to help the poorest of the world’s poor through small loans to start businesses.  A tiny loan can help a woman in the developing world start a business and change the lives of herself and her children by providing a regular source of food, clothing, shelter, and education.  It’s the first step to ending the downward spiral of crushing poverty.

You can help us end poverty with a thoughtful donation by clicking here.

If you have any questions for me in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Join+Us+for+the+2019+Battle+of+the+Sexes.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Join+Us+for+the+2019+Battle+of+the+Sexes.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>The 2019 Battle of the Sexes Tennis Festival is coming up, and we hope to see you all there. Here are the details about the event.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>The 2019 Battle of the Sexes Tennis Festival is coming up, and we hope to see you all there. Here are the details about the event.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why Work With the Monique Walker Team?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-work-with-the-monique-walker-team.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2019-07-16 10:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Why+Work+With+the+Monique+Walker+Team%3F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I’ve been selling real estate for 16 years and my team and I are so grateful for all of our clients who keep coming back to us time and time again. 

I’ve designed our amazing team so that you are always waited on, but you’re never waiting on us. 

Melani Beauregard is a buyer specialist who puts all of her energy into her clients. She treats them like family, she listens, and she executes a plan of action to find them the perfect home.

“I’ve designed our amazing team for you to always be waited on.”

Ann Csincsak is also a buyer specialist on our team. She loves taking buyers out and educating them about the process. A lot of agents will be happy to sell you a house, but not happy to teach you the process. Ann loves teaching her clients and making this a simple process for her client’s busy schedules.

There are a few team mottos we have that are kind of like life mottos. They are:

1. We always do what’s best for the client2. Our performance outsells other agents’ promises3. We’re kind, proactive, aggressive, and very professional agents

If you or someone you know is thinking about purchasing or listing a home any time in the near future, don’t hesitate to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Why+Work+With+the+Monique+Walker+Team%3F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Why+Work+With+the+Monique+Walker+Team%3F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Our team is designed for you. A few of our buyer specialists joined me to explain why.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Our team is designed for you. A few of our buyer specialists joined me to explain why.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Some News About Our Market’s Interest Rates</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/some-news-about-our-markets-interest-rates.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2019-06-28 09:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Some+News+About+Our+Markets+Interest+Rates.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I’m alongside Tom Ross with Bay Equity Home Loans and, together, we’re here to discuss our current interest rate environment. 

By the end of this May, we saw a notable development with regard to interest rates: The combination of tariffs and various other economic conditions are driving rates down, and this downward trend doesn’t look like it’s going to slow or move in the other direction anytime soon.

“The combination of tariffs and various other economic conditions are driving rates down.”

Although market indicators tell us that rates will continue their current trajectory for the next year or so, it’s worth pointing out that, last year, we were confident that rates would continue to rise well into the high-5’s. It wasn’t until the Fed signaled a change of course in their policy decisions early this year that we knew we could see rates flatten out or begin to fall. 

All things considered, conditions are very favorable at this moment, and it’s a great time to get into the market.  

Whether you’re considering buying or refinancing, go ahead and give Tom a call at 602-791-5861. We’d love to help you as a team! And if you have any other questions regarding your real estate needs, please reach out to me as well. We hope to hear from you soon!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Some+News+About+Our+Markets+Interest+Rates.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Some+News+About+Our+Markets+Interest+Rates.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Interest rates are moving in a downward direction and are showing no signs of changing for at least a year—but why? I’m joined by Tom Ross from Bay Equity to answer that.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Interest rates are moving in a downward direction and are showing no signs of changing for at least a year—but why? I’m joined by Tom Ross from Bay Equity to answer that.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>If You Plan on Buying a Home, the Time to Act Is Now</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/if-you-plan-on-buying-home-time-to-act.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2019-06-07 11:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+If+You+Plan+on+Buying+a+Home%2C+the+Time+to+Act+Is+Now.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you’re a homebuyer, the time to buy is now—here’s why.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


Are you waiting for the market to soften to buy a home?

A lot of buyers have this plan because they’re afraid that what happened during the last economic downturn will happen again soon. However, according to my guest today, Tom Ross of Bay Equity Home Loans, the last economic downturn was a once-in-a-century event, and the current market features a totally different set of circumstances.

If you plan on staying in your home for at least three years, there are plenty of underlying reasons why now is a great time to buy.

“The last economic downturn was a once-in-a-century event, and the current market features a totally different set of circumstances.”

According to the statistics, Phoenix is the fastest-growing city in the U.S. Not only are we ranked in the top 10% of all cities in terms of job growth, but we’re also in the top 20% in terms of historical appreciation.

We have about 70,000 households being formed annually, but only 25,000 homes being built. To be exact, we have less than three months of inventory, and we don’t see supply catching up to demand in the foreseeable future. Furthermore, appreciation is also expected to continue to rise.

If you look at the big picture, it’s a great time to buy or sell, so if you plan on doing either anytime soon, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+If+You+Plan+on+Buying+a+Home%2C+the+Time+to+Act+Is+Now.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+If+You+Plan+on+Buying+a+Home%2C+the+Time+to+Act+Is+Now.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you’re a homebuyer, the time to buy is now—here’s why.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you’re a homebuyer, the time to buy is now—here’s why.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Are You Ready to Take Advantage of the Spring Market?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/spring-is-best-time-to-sell-your-home.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2019-04-15 12:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Are+You+Ready+to+Take+Advantage+of+the+Spring+Market%3F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you’ve been thinking of selling your home, now’s your chance!


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


When is the largest number of homes sold? In springtime, of course! And since it’s now officially spring, it’s the perfect season to jump into our thriving real estate market.

We see the most sales from April to June, so now’s the time to prepare for listing your home. If you or someone you know is thinking of selling soon, I’m here to help—I’d be more than happy to give you a home estimate and help you find the perfect buyer.

Give me a call at 602-413-8195 or send an email to Monique@MoniqueSells.com, and let’s begin the home selling journey together. I look forward to hearing from you soon!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Are+You+Ready+to+Take+Advantage+of+the+Spring+Market%3F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Are+You+Ready+to+Take+Advantage+of+the+Spring+Market%3F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you’ve been thinking of selling your home, now’s your chance!

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you’ve been thinking of selling your home, now’s your chance!

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Thank You For Your Support</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/thank-you-for-your-support.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Gives Back</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2019-03-29 14:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Today we’d like to thank you for trusting us with your real estate needs.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


Whether you’ve bought or sold a home with us before, follow our messages, or have supported our business in any other way, we’ve got a simple message to share with you today: Thank you. Our team has helped more than 40 of you achieve your real estate goals so far, and we’re so fortunate to have the opportunity to serve our community in this way. Business is thriving, and it wouldn’t be possible without you. To see our full message of gratitude, watch this short video.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Today we’d like to thank you for trusting us with your real estate needs.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Today we’d like to thank you for trusting us with your real estate needs.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Would You Be Surprised to Know?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/would-you-be-surprised-to-know.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2019-02-07 14:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Would+You+Be+Surprised+to+Know_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

How will these changes in our market affect you? You may be, well, surprised!


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


Our market is simply full of surprises lately!

First of all, though we’re still in a seller’s market, we’re currently experiencing the largest inventory of homes we’ve seen in a long time. Our number of months of inventory—or how long it takes to sell all homes currently on the market—is at 3.06.

“Our market could be balancing out.”

On top of this, in the last 30 days, we’ve had the lowest number of homes sold. Together, these factors mean that our market could be balancing out. It also means that it’s now easier for people to sell their homes and purchase new ones.

As each area has its own unique market, so if you want to find out more about your specific neighborhood, your best bet is to give us a call. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Would+You+Be+Surprised+to+Know_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Would+You+Be+Surprised+to+Know_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

How will these changes in our market affect you? You may be, well, surprised!

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

How will these changes in our market affect you? You may be, well, surprised!

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Giving Back to Our Heroes</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/giving-back-to-our-heroes.html</link>
        
          <category>Charity</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-03 15:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Giving+Back+to+Our+Heroes.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We’re excited to announce our new program that will allow us to give back to the heroes in our community. Learn how it works here.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


I’m here today with my preferred lender, Tom Ross of Bay Equity, and we’ve been talking about how we can give back to our community, particularly to the people who have and still serve us in the community.

I’m so excited because we finally have a program designed to do just that: Giving to Heroes. Who qualifies as a hero? In this context, a hero could be any person who dedicates their lives to serving us in the community—such as a teacher, a nurse, a firefighter, a police officer, an active duty military serviceperson, a veteran, or, slightly controversially, an employee of the government sector.

“We’re so excited to be able to contribute and give back.”

With this program, we’re able to contribute toward these heroes’ closing costs as our little way of thanking them for spending their lives serving us. We’re so excited to be able to contribute and give back.

If you have any lending questions for Tom, he can be reached at (602) 791-5861 or at tross@bayeq.comtross@bayeq.com.

If you’re curious about purchasing a property and you’re a hero, please feel free to reach out to us. We would love to serve you back.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Giving+Back+to+Our+Heroes.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Giving+Back+to+Our+Heroes.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

We’re excited to announce our new program that will allow us to give back to the heroes in our community. Learn how it works here.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

We’re excited to announce our new program that will allow us to give back to the heroes in our community. Learn how it works here.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Respond to Rising Interest Rates</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-respond-to-rising-interest-rates.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2018-10-24 13:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+How+to+Respond+to+Rising+Interest+Rates.mp4</guid>
        <description>

What should you do about interest rates knowing that they’re on the rise? Tom Ross from Bay Equity is here to explain.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


I’m here today with my preferred lender, Tom Ross from Bay Equity, to discuss a question about interest rates: “What should you do about interest rates, knowing that they’re on the rise?”

Tom’s short answer is: Lock your rate in now.

People have it in their head that if they just wait long enough, they’ll end up with a lower rate eventually. But rates in the 3% area are long gone; at our highest this year, we’ve brushed 5% and came back down into the high fours. This time next year, the 4% rates will be long gone as well.

“Try not to turn down any showings, if possible.”

Those in the market need to wrap their heads around the fact that this climb in rates we’re going into will be long-term and sustained. We’re in the midst of a sort of trade war with China, and inflation tends to raise interest rates as well. In fact, the Federal Reserve has gone on record to say that they’re going to raise the federal funds rate at least four times between now and the end of next year. Two of those jumps might occur even before the end of this year.

Now the federal funds rate doesn’t directly impact mortgage rates, but as it rises, you tend to see interest rates come up.

If you have any questions for Tom about rising interest rates, you can reach him at Bay Equity by calling (602) 791-5861 or by sending an email to tross@bayeq.com.

For any questions about real estate in general, we always encourage you to reach out to us here at RE/MAX Excalibur. We’d love to answer your questions.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+How+to+Respond+to+Rising+Interest+Rates.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+How+to+Respond+to+Rising+Interest+Rates.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

What should you do about interest rates knowing that they’re on the rise? Tom Ross from Bay Equity is here to explain.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

What should you do about interest rates knowing that they’re on the rise? Tom Ross from Bay Equity is here to explain.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Safety Tips For Selling a Vacant Home</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-stay-safe-when-listing-vacant.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2018-09-11 11:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+How+to+Stay+Safe+When+Listing+a+Vacant+Home.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you’re listing a vacant home, there are certain safety tips you will need to follow.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


When selling a vacant home, following certain safety tips will be essential. Today, we’ll be sharing seven such tips:


  
    Set up a security system.
  
  
    Install motion sensors and timed lighting.
  
  
    Ask a friend or neighbor to keep a car parked in your driveway.
  
  
    Have someone routinely pick up your mail.
  
  
    Maintain your landscaping.
  
  
    Keep blinds and curtains closed.
  
  
    Check on the property after storms.
  


Following these tips will help keep you and your asset protected during the listing process.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+How+to+Stay+Safe+When+Listing+a+Vacant+Home.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+How+to+Stay+Safe+When+Listing+a+Vacant+Home.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you’re listing a vacant home, there are certain safety tips you will need to follow.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you’re listing a vacant home, there are certain safety tips you will need to follow.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>5 Top Home Selling Tips</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/5-top-home-selling-tips.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2018-08-27 15:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+5+Top+Home+Selling+Tips.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We’ve got plenty of tips for potential home sellers out there. Here are five of them.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


Are you in the process of getting your house ready to put on the market? If so, here are a few tips to help you:

1. Don’t overprice your home. Pricing is everything when marketing your home for sale. Even a well-priced home with a bad marketing plan will sell, but an overpriced home won’t.

2. Failing to make repairs. If the dog chewed something up or there are other minor damages that a buyer would spot immediately, get those fixed before you get the property listed and start taking pictures.

3. Neglecting to declutter your home. If you have a lot of personal items, boxes, or general clutter, that’s one of the first things a buyer will notice. As part of our services, we bring a professional stager out to our buyers’ properties to help declutter and stage the property.

“Try not to turn down any showings, if possible.”

4. Don’t turn down showings. To get your home sold quickly and for top dollar, it should be about when it’s most convenient for an agent to show your property, not the other way around.

5. Getting overly emotional about your home. Think of your home as a property or an asset than as your home. This shift in mindset will help you maximize the sale price.

If you have any questions for me or want to know why my performance outsells all those promises out there, give me a call or send me an email today. I look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+5+Top+Home+Selling+Tips.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+5+Top+Home+Selling+Tips.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

We’ve got plenty of tips for potential home sellers out there. Here are five of them.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

We’ve got plenty of tips for potential home sellers out there. Here are five of them.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Do Agents Earn Their Commission?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-do-agents-earn-their-commission.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2018-08-07 15:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+How+Do+Agents+Earn+Their+Commission.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you are wondering how an agent earns their commission, here is a rundown of everything we do for our clients.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


How do we agents earn our commission? There are six important ways:


  
    We identify and solve problems quickly by providing solutions to our clients.
  
  
    We pre-qualify buyers. If I am your listing agent, it is my job to ask buyers the right questions so you can go under contract with one who is fully qualified and can close within the escrow period.
  
  
    We manage expectations. I need to manage expectations for my clients so they know what the process is like and we can work together to execute it properly.
  


“My ultimate goal is to get them the most amount of money in the least amount of time.”


  
    We have communication skills. We have to communicate with both our clients and the public at large. We get paid to tell the truth, which is difficult sometimes because of market conditions we have no control over. Part of these communication skills also involves forecasting what’s to come in our market in the near future.
  
  
    We can find buyers for our seller clients. One of my favorite things to do in my job is prospect for buyers.
  
  
    We can effectively and efficiently guide buyers and sellers through the whole home sale process. I have a full-service team working with me, and our whole goal is to prevent clients from waiting on me. Rather, my team should be waiting on them.
  


When people hire me, my ultimate goal is to get them the most amount of money in the least amount of time.

If you would like to know more about how I am able to accomplish this goal or you have any other real estate questions, please feel free to reach out to me. I would love to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+How+Do+Agents+Earn+Their+Commission.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+How+Do+Agents+Earn+Their+Commission.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

If you are wondering how an agent earns their commission, here is a rundown of everything we do for our clients.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

If you are wondering how an agent earns their commission, here is a rundown of everything we do for our clients.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Questions Your Agent Should Be Able to Answer</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-questions-your-agent-should-be-able.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2018-07-20 14:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+3+Questions+Your+Agent+Should+Be+Able+to+Answer.mp4</guid>
        <description>

How can you determine whether your listing agent is the right choice to help you sell your home? Start with these three questions.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


Today we are going to talk about the three most important questions that you should be asking your listing agent:

1. What is my home worth? A good listing agent should be able to tell you what you should list the home for and what it will sell for within a couple of percentage points.

“The agent should have a specific marketing plan that will attract the most possible buyers.”

2. How long will it take to sell my home? They should also be able to show you the average time on market for your area and what their own average is based on past sales.

3. What will you do do get the property sold? There should be a specific marketing plan that will attract the most possible buyers and get your home sold quickly.

I would be happy to go over my answers to these questions with you. If you would like to know them or if you have any other questions about the market, please feel free to give me a call or send me an email today. I would love to hear from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+3+Questions+Your+Agent+Should+Be+Able+to+Answer.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+3+Questions+Your+Agent+Should+Be+Able+to+Answer.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

How can you determine whether your listing agent is the right choice to help you sell your home? Start with these three questions.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

How can you determine whether your listing agent is the right choice to help you sell your home? Start with these three questions.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Has Our Market Been Doing Recently?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-has-our-market-been-doing-recently.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2018-06-08 14:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+How+Has+Our+Market+Been+Doing+Recently%253F+(1).mp4</guid>
        <description>

It is time to take a look at the latest market conditions. But alongside today’s update, allow me to also share a great, new listing.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


It is time to take a look back at our April real estate market. But before we get into those statistics, I want to tell you about a great new listing.

Located at 3542 East Hazelwood Street, this 4-bed, 2-bath Phoenix property is one you will certainly want to check out for yourself. To see photos of this 2,000 square-foot, $675,000 home, click here.

“We are still in a strong seller’s market.”

Now let’s get back to discussing our market. Currently, we are still in a strong seller’s market. As of April, there were 10% fewer homes on the market than in April of 2017. And there were 4% more sales year over year, as well.

If you have any other questions, would like more information, or are curious about how market conditions will impact your real estate goals, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+How+Has+Our+Market+Been+Doing+Recently%253F+(1).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+How+Has+Our+Market+Been+Doing+Recently%253F+(1).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

It is time to take a look at the latest market conditions. But alongside today’s update, allow me to also share a great, new listing.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

It is time to take a look at the latest market conditions. But alongside today’s update, allow me to also share a great, new listing.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What 3 Questions Do You Need to Ask Every Agent?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-3-questions-do-you-need-to-ask.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2018-05-07 14:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+What+3+Questions+Do+You+Need+to+Ask+Every+Agent%253F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Before hiring a real estate agent, you need to do some vetting. Here are the questions that we recommend you ask.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


Selling or buying a home can be one of the largest transactions of your life. A trusted consultant and Realtor can be an invaluable partner to have. When you interview a Realtor to hire, here are three really good questions to ask them:

1. “How many homes have you sold in the last 12 months?” It’s interesting to find out how long an agent has been in the market, but noting their productivity in the last 12 months is a better indicator of whether or not they are a productive, full-time agent.

“You want to get a sense that this agent is somebody you can trust.”

2. “Can I have the contact info for your last three deals?” This question may be a surprise to the agent, but it could provide you with an honest, authentic answer to help you feel comfortable with them.

3. “What specific strategies are you going to use to get my home sold?” Some agents specialize in buyer sales. Some agents specialize in listing and selling. A specific, proven plan is essential for any buyer or seller.

To get my answers to these questions and more, feel free to reach out and give me a call or send me an email. I would love to hear from you today.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+What+3+Questions+Do+You+Need+to+Ask+Every+Agent%253F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+What+3+Questions+Do+You+Need+to+Ask+Every+Agent%253F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Before hiring a real estate agent, you need to do some vetting. Here are the questions that we recommend you ask.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Before hiring a real estate agent, you need to do some vetting. Here are the questions that we recommend you ask.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Reasons to Sell Your Phoenix Home This Spring</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-reasons-to-sell-your-phoenix-home.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2018-04-18 16:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+3+Reasons+to+Sell+Your+Phoenix+Home+This+Spring.mp4</guid>
        <description>

This spring is a great time to sell your Phoenix home. Here are three reasons why.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


Spring is my favorite time to sell real estate. If you are looking to sell your home, there are three reasons why we are in a very strong seller’s market right now:

1. Demand continues to increase while inventory remains low. The number of homes for sale is down 8% year over year. Why? The job outlook is strong, and more millennials are coming into the market.

2. Home prices are still surging. We have appreciated 6% year over year, and I don’t see that changing anytime soon.

“Our current market is great for both buyers and sellers.”

3. Interest rates are rising. Right now, interest rates are at 4.5% for a 30-year fixed mortgage. Although that is a three-year high for interest rates, it is still historically low and very affordable for buyers. I don’t know how much longer this favorable situation will last.

If you are looking to sell your home, now is a great time. Demand is high and prices are high, so our current market is very favorable for sellers.

If you’re interested in finding out what your home is worth, we would be happy to come by and let you know what we can sell it for, how long it’s going to take, and what we’ll do to make that happen.

If you have any other real estate questions, please don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I would be happy to help you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+3+Reasons+to+Sell+Your+Phoenix+Home+This+Spring.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+3+Reasons+to+Sell+Your+Phoenix+Home+This+Spring.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

This spring is a great time to sell your Phoenix home. Here are three reasons why.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

This spring is a great time to sell your Phoenix home. Here are three reasons why.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Do You Want to Buy or Sell Outside of Arizona?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/do-you-want-to-buy-or-sell-outside-of.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
          <category>Home Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2018-02-15 12:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Do+You+Want+to+Buy+or+Sell+Outside+of+Arizona%253F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you’ve ever thought about buying or selling real estate outside of Arizona, I would be more than happy to connect you with the right Realtor for the job.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


As you will see in the background of today’s video, I’m definitely not in Arizona. Actually, I’m coming to you from San Diego for a real estate conference with 2,000 of the very best Realtors in North America. So if you’re looking to buy or sell property outside of Arizona, call me and let me connect you with the very best Realtor for the job. To see my full message, watch this short video.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Do+You+Want+to+Buy+or+Sell+Outside+of+Arizona%253F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Do+You+Want+to+Buy+or+Sell+Outside+of+Arizona%253F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>The 2018 Market Is Already Full of Opportunities</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-2018-market-is-already-full-of.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2018-02-02 14:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+The+2018+Market+Is+Already+Full+of+Opportunities.mp4</guid>
        <description>

What do you need to know about our 2018 market so far? Let’s find out in our first update of the year.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


Happy New Year! Now that we’ve entered into 2018, it’s time for us to have our first market update of the year. Our current market is great for both buyers and sellers.

Sellers should know that we have 10% less inventory right now than we did last year. This means less competition for you.

“Our current market is great for both buyers and sellers.”

It’s also a great time to buy because interest rates are still hovering around lows of around 4%. As always, I’m here to help you with whatever your real estate needs may be.

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+The+2018+Market+Is+Already+Full+of+Opportunities.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+The+2018+Market+Is+Already+Full+of+Opportunities.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

What do you need to know about our 2018 market so far? Let’s find out in our first update of the year.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

What do you need to know about our 2018 market so far? Let’s find out in our first update of the year.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Homes Are More Affordable Now in Phoenix</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/homes-are-more-affordable-now-in-phoenix.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Real Estate Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2017-12-21 11:28:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Homes+Are+More+Affordable+Now+in+Phoenix.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Buying power has just gone up in Maricopa County. Tom Ross is here with the latest news.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


I’m back once again with my preferred lender, Tom Ross of Bay Equity, to give you guys some important new information about mortgage loan limits here in Phoenix. Some big changes have come out this last week and we wanted to explain what was going on to you guys.

Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac have both raised their loan limits for conventional financing to $453,100 in Maricopa County. What this means is that you can essentially buy a $477,000 home with only 5% down.

“Your buying power has increased as a result.”

It’s a big assist to the buying power of anybody who is looking to buy a home with conventional financing. It opens up the market a bit more as well.

If you have any interest in buying a home or just want to know more about these loan increases, give us a call or send us an email. We would love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Homes+Are+More+Affordable+Now+in+Phoenix.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Homes+Are+More+Affordable+Now+in+Phoenix.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Buying power has just gone up in Maricopa County. Tom Ross is here with the latest news.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Buying power has just gone up in Maricopa County. Tom Ross is here with the latest news.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Having Mortgage Trouble? Dont Worry - Help Is Available</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/having-mortgage-trouble-dont-worry-help.html</link>
        
          <category>Arizona Real Estate Mortgage Advice</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2017-11-21 13:46:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Having+Mortgage+Trouble%253F+Dont+Worry+-+Help+Is+Available.mp4</guid>
        <description>

One Home at a Time Housing Solutions can help anyone facing difficulties making their mortgage payments.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


Today I’m joined by special guest Maurice Brundidge of One Home at a Time Housing Solutions to discuss how they can assist anyone who has missed several mortgage payments and is facing foreclosure.

First, Maurice and his company perform a financial assessment of that individual or family to determine whether they can realistically afford to keep their house. If they can, they’ll put together a financial package that they can submit to their lender to request a loan modification. This package will consist of a hardship letter, their financial documents, and the lender application.

If your application for a loan modification was turned down and you found the process intimidating or frustrating, they’ll make the experience much easier the second time around.

“We know that life happens, but there are options out there for you.”

If you’re on the verge of missing a payment, Maurice’s first piece of advice is to contact your lender and inform them of your situation. Lenders have programs in their imminent default area that will consider a loan modification on your behalf before you become a delinquent.

If you previously received a modification and you’re on the verge of becoming a delinquent again, you can apply for another modification, but you can’t apply for the same reason as your previous application.

We know that life happens, but there are options out there for you that can allow you to keep your home. If you’d like to get in touch with Maurice or would like a free consultation from him, just give him a call at (602) 703-4228.

If you have any more questions for us about this topic or want to know what’s going on in our market, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’d be glad to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Having+Mortgage+Trouble%253F+Dont+Worry+-+Help+Is+Available.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Having+Mortgage+Trouble%253F+Dont+Worry+-+Help+Is+Available.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

One Home at a Time Housing Solutions can help anyone facing difficulties making their mortgage payments.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

One Home at a Time Housing Solutions can help anyone facing difficulties making their mortgage payments.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Are Cash Offers Always the Best Option?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/are-cash-offers-always-best-option.html</link>
        
          <category>Phoenix Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2017-10-26 15:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+When+should+you+accept+a+cash+offer%253F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Is a cash offer always best? Not always. I’ll go over when a cash offer is and isn’t necessarily your best option when selling your home.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


As a seller, is a cash offer always your best option? You may be surprised, but the answer is no.

Cash offers are great if you need a fast close and don’t care about getting the absolute best price the market will bare. However, if you do want top dollar for your home sale, we will take about 90 days from start to finish.

“We know how to find you the right buyer.”

We know how to find you the right buyer in either situation. Whether you have time or need a quick close, we’ll make sure you get everything you want out of your home sale.

If you are looking to buy or sell a home, or if you have any questions, don’t hesitate to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+When+should+you+accept+a+cash+offer%253F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+When+should+you+accept+a+cash+offer%253F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Is a cash offer always best? Not always. I’ll go over when a cash offer is and isn’t necessarily your best option when selling your home.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Is a cash offer always best? Not always. I’ll go over when a cash offer is and isn’t necessarily your best option when selling your home.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Support The Guerrant Foundations Worthwhile Cause</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/support-guerrant-foundations-worthwhile.html</link>
        
          <category>Battle of the Sexes</category>
        
        <author>Monique Walker</author>
        <pubDate>2017-10-10 11:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Support+the+Guerrant+Foundations+Worthwhile+Cause.mp4</guid>
        <description>

The 8th Annual Battle of the Sexes Tennis Festival is coming soon. This year, 100% of proceeds are being matched by The Guerrant Foundation.


Buying a Phoenix Home? Search all Homes for Sale
Selling a Phoenix Home? Check out our FREE Home Value Report


Anne Guerrant has traveled the globe as a professional tennis player. During her travels, what she saw in much of the developing world appalled her. Debilitating poverty. Families living on less than $1 a day.

Anne and her husband, Terry, started The Guerrant Foundation to help these people by giving them small loans to start businesses. They make it easy for many people to be part of something bigger than themselves.

The Guerrant Foundation’s biggest fundraiser of the year is coming up. The 8th Annual Battle of the Sexes Tennis Festival will be held on Saturday, November 4th from 2 p.m. to 4 p.m. at The Phoenician (6000 E Camelback Road). This year, Anne and Terry are matching 100% of all the donations they receive and all of that money is going directly to help these budding entrepreneurs.

“This year’s event will be held on November 4th from 2 p.m. to 4 p.m.”

The loans they provide aren’t hand-outs, they are hand-ups. The loans go to smart, capable, driven entrepreneurs who need just a little bit of capital to achieve liftoff. Since the foundation started, Anne and Terry have been able to help thousands of people around the globe write a new chapter in their family’s life.

To donate, go to: https://www.youcaring.com/WalkerBattleoftheSexes

If you have any questions about the event, check out The Guerrant Foundation’s website here. We’re proud sponsors of this event and we look forward to seeing you there! If you have any other real estate questions in the meantime, don’t hesitate to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Support+the+Guerrant+Foundations+Worthwhile+Cause.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Monique+Walker/+VIdeos/Phoenix+Real+Estate-+Support+the+Guerrant+Foundations+Worthwhile+Cause.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

The 8th Annual Battle of the Sexes Tennis Festival is coming soon. This year, 100% of proceeds are being matched by The Guerrant Foundation.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Monique Walker</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

The 8th Annual Battle of the Sexes Tennis Festival is coming soon. This year, 100% of proceeds are being matched by The Guerrant Foundation.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Phoenix, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Monique Walker</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Monique Walker</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Monique Walker Team - your professional Phoenix Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
